Cyriac Jannel

www.cyriacjannel.com c.jannel@lecolededesign.com @cyriacjannel

User Experience Design Student

◆ Nantes, France

Profile

I am currently in the fourth year of Master's degree program in Information Design and User Experience Design at l'École de Design Nantes Atlantique. Curious and motivated, I like to design interfaces and to solve problems by digital solutions.

Education

Bachelor's Degree in Interaction Design

École de design Nantes Atlantique - Nantes, France 2015 - 2017

Two years of undergraduate program specialize in interaction design.

- Design of interactive digital user experience and user interfaces, web and mobile app, information and knowledge management systems & graphic user interface.
- Web programing languages (HTML 5 / CSS 3).
- 3D modeling and real-time computer graphic design with Unity.

Foundation studies

École de design Nantes Atlantique - Nantes, France 2014 - 2015

Basic skills in design and applied arts.

- Practical workshops in packaging, graphic design, spatial design, interactivity and product design.
- · Learned the different design professions.

Baccalauréat in economics and social science

Lycée Saint-Blaise - Douarnenez, France 2014 - 2015

- Social sciences, Philosophy and humanities in management and business administration, and in economics.
- History & Geography and Mathematics.

Professional experience

User Experience Design Intern

Anchovy - Ħamrun, Malta Sep 2017 - Dec 2017 • 4 mos

- Data and user flow analyze with Google Analytics.
- Full journey specification including acquisition channels (social media advertisement).
- User experience to optimize existing products and user interface design, working with graphic designers to create or improve visual identity.

User Experience Design Intern

Agorize - Paris, France Jul 2016 - Oct 2016 • 4 mos

- Design of interfaces, user paths in wireframes and reflections about the user experience.
- Worked on the user interface of the website and improvement of the visual identity, in an integrated team, composed of developers, designers and testers.

Skills

Design

Sketch - Very good knowledge Illustrator - Good knowledge Photoshop - Good knowledge

Prototype

After Effect - Very good knowledge Principle - Good knowledge Flinto - Good knowledge

Code

HTML 5 / CSS 3 - Good knowledge Javascript - Basic knowledge

Languages

French - Native language English - Good knowledge German - Basic knowledge

Interests & Hobbies



Video games

Half-Life, Journey, Transport Tycoon, RollerCoaster Tycoon...



Literature

1984, Planet of the Apes, The Road, Metro 2033...



Street Art

Banksy, M. Chat, Os Gemeos, JR, Slinkachu, Eine...



Salsa Music

Buena Vista Social Club, Compay Segundo, Afro-Cuban All Stars...

References available on request.